

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





Rohan Powar Rohan Powar Rohan Powar ASAP JOINER!! 8 yrs totl exp (5.5 yrs Workday ERP) CSPO® Certified Scrum Product Owner, Workday HCM functional & configuration, Workday Production support & Business Analytics, HR IT Service Delivery, Global team, Workday projects, PMP, Agile Scrum Current Location: Mumbai Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Pref. Location: Mumba Notice Period: 15 Days or less Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [Human Resource] Maintenance Role: Business Analyst Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried Key Skills: CSPO, workday functional, workday analyst, hris, agile project management, workday customer, workday client, workday maintenance, workday support, as ap joiner, immediate joiner, business analytics, service management,hcm,certified scrum product owner, Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

#### Summary

Jump to Section

ASAP JOINER!! 8 yrs totl exp (5.5 yrs on Workday ERP) mr.powar@gmail.com 8097456637 CSPO® Certified Scrum Product Owner, Workday HCM functional configuration, Workday projects, Workday Production support & Business Analyst, HR IT Service Delivery, Global team, PMP, Agile Scrum

### **Work Experience**

Alight Solutions as Workday IT Developer Analyst (Manager) Sep 2019 to Nov 2019

'ALIGHT SOLUTIONS': September'19-November'19 Business title: Workday IT Developer Analyst 1

Department: Customer Workday Application Management System

Job level: Manager

Workday HCM functional configuration - Release Management - Business Analytics - Workday Projects: Configuration, implementation Workday HCM, EIB Integrations, Benefits/Time Off Plans, Absence, WD Learning,

Business Process, Custom Reports etc

Workday product ownership. Working with Workday Dev Team (on Scrum which is an Agile) framework for developing, delivering, and sustaining products

Follow up meetings, Data gathering, negotiation and finalizing strategy, Sign-Off and Documentation for Go-Live strategy

Reviewing Change Requests, Service delivery according to agreed SLAs in terms of availability, quality, HCM functionality

Simultaneously running projects which involved extensive synchronization between Workday Dev Team and Stakeholders

Working with Technology Partners and Stakeholder for updates, enhancements, bug fixes and integrations Service life-cycle covering both functional and some technical road-maps as well as roll-out schedules Release management - for Workday HCM, Configuration, Security and Integration Change Management - Working on change requests raised by Stakeholder

Hotelbeds Group as Global Workday Analyst Aug 2017 to Aug 2019

'HOTELBEDS GROUP': August'17 - August'19 (2 Years) Business title: Global Workday Analyst Department: Workday Development and Data Analytics Job level: Deputy Manager

Workday HCM functional configuration - Ongoing Production Support:

Configure, implement, maintain & troubleshoot Custom Reports, Configuring Calculated Fields, Eligibility Rules,

Report scheduling, Dashboard Creation

Building Integration Systems, Document Transformation, Workday Web Services Outbound/Inbound Integrations (CCW: Core Connector Worker)

# **Important**

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Onsite training deliveries to Spain - Hotelbeds Head office. Topics: Workday Modules - Absence Mgmt, Time Off, Reporting, Business Process

Performs testing activities to ensure development/configuration work meets user requirements, such as functional testing, end-user testing

Configuration, implement, maintain & troubleshoot:- Benefit Plan, Compensation Plan, Business Process & Custom Reports

Workday bi-annual feature release analysis and testing. New feature implementation & Test execution and reporting

Run ElB (Enterprise Interface Builder), Independently investigates ElB Error Summary and can re-launch ElB

Biannual feature release - User Acceptance Testing (UAT) and feature release buy-in

Understands workday Tenant Security. Knows Role Assignment task and their impact

Assisting and Providing Level 4 Support on HR Technology issues to the Stakeholder

Worked on (Application Tracking System) IBM Kenexa Brassring

# Travelex India Pvt Ltd as HR Operations Specialist

Apr 2014 to Aug 2017

'TRAVELEX INDIA PVT LTD': Apr'14 - Aug'17 (3.4 Years)

Business title: HR Operations Specialist (Workday HCM)

Department: HROS Human Resources Operation Services / HR Tech / HR IT / HRSS (Human Resources Shared Services)

Workday HR Transactional & Administrative Support:

Set-Up Values - Set-Up values creation for Cost Centre/ Location/ Sup Orgs/Pay group/Compensation Element/External Payroll Earning/One-time Payment

Restructuring - Re-structuring of Organization Structure/Reorganization for respective managers in different markets (APAC/EMEA/NAM/CE)

Generation of letters for various regions i.e. Termination, Change in contract, Air side pass, Reference, Probation, Maternity, Disciplinary

Developed user procedures, guidelines and documentation. Training/assisting HRBP and Team members on new processes/functionality

Query Management -Troubleshoot/Investigate integration, core HCM issues, test, and resolving technical queries faced by end users

Developed user procedures, guidelines and documentation. Trained HRBP and Team members on new processes/functionality

System account creation & Activation, Supporting Performance Management, Change Management, SharePoint Management

Managing global employee queries/issues pertaining to pay, compensations, time off, policies, time tracking, overtime etc

Working across departmental lines to resolve issues and improve current processes, Workday audits & HR Audits Supporting Recruitment team for on boarding in Workday related to open job reg, positions, movement etc

Working closely with Managers, HR Business partner & Heads to close employee grievances, issues

Managing Confirmation, Probation process & Visa Expiry process, Managing HRIS query mailbox

Absence Management - Configuration of plans in Workday & Providing post go live support

Prepare, maintain and update employee data for the HR information system - Workday

Managing Background verification, References for UK & US market

Managing Ceridian and HR Evolution systems for UK Payroll support

#### TCS (TATA Consultancy Services) as HR Retainer

Aug 2012 to Apr 2013

'TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES': Aug'12 - April'13 (0.9 Years Contract)

Business title: HR Retainer

Department: HRSS Human Resources Shared Services

Role & Responsibility: International HR Operations, HR Systems, Business Analysis

#### Aditya Birla Group Retail Ltd as HR Coordinator

Jan 2012 to Jul 2012

'ADITYA BIRLA RETAIL GROUP': Jan'12 - July12 (0.7 Years)

Business title: HR Coordinator (Corporate Office)

Department: Corporate HR Team

Role & Responsibility. HR Partner and Onboarding

^ Back to Top

### Education

UG: B.Sc (General) from University of Mumbai, Mumbai in 2008

PG: MBA/PGDM (Human Resource) from Atharva Institute of Management Studies, Mumbai in 2011

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:
Advanced MS Excel Training & Passed with 'A' Grade
PMP® Certificate Exam Preparatory Training
SAP HR ECC 6.0
CSPO® Certified Scrum Product Owner

^ Back to Top

# IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Workday Functional Configuration		5 Year(s)
, ,		. ,
PROJECT MANAGEMENT		5 Year(s)
Certified Scrum Product Owner		1 Year(s)
PMP		4 Year(s)
AGILE		1 Year(s)

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Marathi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

### **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.